  contact                  5b42010 safe to reset, wip for prod
  dev                      0873829 safe to rest, made changes in homepage scroll animation
* homepage                 73156c8 safe to reset, WIP on homepage
  main                     5b42010 safe to reset, wip for prod
  mobile                   fe38af4 safe to reset, made changes in mobile outlet, bug fixes and deleted log and testing files
  remotes/origin/contact   5b42010 safe to reset, wip for prod
  remotes/origin/dev       0873829 safe to rest, made changes in homepage scroll animation
  remotes/origin/footer    1a76a1e Not safe to reset, WIP
  remotes/origin/hardcoded f92e317 safe to reset, scaffolding done right
  remotes/origin/homepage  0873829 safe to rest, made changes in homepage scroll animation
  remotes/origin/main      bdce8ba Enhanced Homepage
  remotes/origin/mobile    fe38af4 safe to reset, made changes in mobile outlet, bug fixes and deleted log and testing files
  remotes/origin/studio    6a833b6 safe to reset, made changes in teams page
